Well, they say that time flies when you're having fun, and it certainly feels like time is flying.
즐거운 시간은 쏜살같이 흘러간다고들 하잖아요 정말 시간이 쏜살같이 흘러가는 것 같아요
Uh, hopefully for you as well as for me.
저와 여러분을 위해서요
Uh, you have reached the 20% milestone.
20% 이정표에 도달했어요
You were a fifth of the way towards being an expert in all things LMN, and I hope that it feels that
LMN에 관한 모든 것의 5분의 1을 알게 되었어요 그렇게 느끼셨으면 좋겠어요
way.
여러분이 성취감을 느끼길 바라요 레벨을 높이는 과정도요
Every time we get to these summary pages and think about all of the new skills you've acquired.
요약 페이지를 볼 때마다 새로운 기술이 떠오르죠 Get it
So to recap them, I know I keep doing this, but I do think it's important.
요약하자면, 계속 이러지만 중요한 것 같아요
You can of course describe transformers and tokens and contacts, windows and API prices and all of
변압기, 토큰, 연락처, 윈도우, API 가격 등을 설명하실 수 있어요
You can code now pretty confidently, I would say with the different APIs for the frontier models that
꽤 자신 있게 코드를 작성할 수 있어요 여러분이 잘 아는 프론티어 모델에 대한 다양한
you know well, and you can build an AI chatbot assistant, including an interactive UI.
API로요 대화형 UI를 포함한 인공지능 챗봇 비서를 만들 수도 있죠
And I promise you it would be easy.
내가 장담하는데 쉬울 거예요
And it was easy.
식은 죽 먹기였죠
You hopefully you weren't expecting it to be quite as easy as it was.
이렇게 쉬울 줄은 몰랐길 바라요
The one line of code is insane.
코드 한 줄이 정말 대단해요
Uh, that is the, uh, the the wonder, the magic of Gradio.
그게 바로 그래디오의 마법이죠
So next time we change subject to something called tools, which is a particularly interesting capability.
다음엔 도구라는 것으로 주제를 바꾸죠 아주 흥미로운 기능이에요
It's it allows us to give LMS powers to do something, to run some functionality that we will arm it
LMS가 뭔가 하도록 권한을 줍니다 일부 기능을 실행해 코드를
with so we can write some code, and then we can give the arm the ability to, to use it.
작성할 수 있도록요 그런 다음 사용 권한을 주죠
Now that might sound a bit spooky.
비트 박스는 좀 으스스하네요
We're actually going to build something and then sort of give the LMS powers to to to do it.
실제로 뭔가를 구축하고 LMS에게 권한을 주는 거죠
What to like run code on our box.
박스에 코드를 실행하는 거죠
We're going to let them do that.
그렇게 하도록 둘 거예요
Um, and unfortunately, I will warn you, this is one of those things that that sounds very magical.
불행히도 미리 경고하는데 마법처럼 들리는 그런 거예요
And then a bit like the wizard behind the curtain.
커튼 뒤의 마법사처럼 비트를 입었죠
Uh, when you find out what this actually means, it's a little bit less magical when you know the ingredients
비트가 무슨 뜻인지 알게 되면 그 놀라운 요리의 재료를 알게 되면
to the incredible, uh, dish.
마법 같은 느낌이 덜해져요
Suddenly, uh, you think, is that all?
갑자기 그게 다인가 싶더군요
But for the moment, you can you can live in awe of the fact that next time we are going to empower,
하지만 지금은 경외심을 가지셔도 좋습니다 다음번에는
uh, frontier model with the ability to run code on our box, which is going to do things, uh, and
개척 모델에게 권한을 부여할 테니까요 컴퓨터에 코드를 실행할 수 있고
I'm going to reveal the, the secret sauce behind that.
그 뒤에 숨겨진 비밀도 밝혀낼 거예요
And then perhaps it won't be quite as mysterious as it sounds, but I'm excited to take you through
그렇게 되면 생각만큼 신비롭진 않겠지만 여러분을 안내하게 돼서 기뻐요
that.
다음 시간에도 그렇게 할 거예요 그때 봐요